it's now time for tonight's hash
wol
well it is after midnight which means it
is now officially and technically Star
Wars
day let
me let me be the first person on
television to say May the fourth be with
you now last year on Star Wars day I met
the famous mostely Cantina Band figurin
Dan in the modal nodes um I used to be
their lead singer until I went solo heyo
uh we're going to come up with some jams
from a long time ago in a galaxy far far
away with tonight's hashtag Star Wars
songs examples might be wind beneath my
X-Wing and get out of my dreams get into
my Carbonite I'm going to put 60 seconds
on the clock and begin Randy uh Yoda one
that I want point oh that's
fantastic points Josh hline bling yes
points Kyle Like a Virgin
oh God damn
it no
points I take that personally I've
touched a lady uh Randy uh trap Queen
amadala by Boba fety WAP points very
good kle K name have you ever really
loved a woman God damn
it son of a I'll give you points
but I don't like it Randy Obi-Wan is the
loneliest
number
J Nothing Compares R2D2 you yes
Point Kyle Dancing with Myself God damn
it
points M money mo tontons
points Randy
r2d Two Princes by kylo Ren doctor nice
very well done points Kyle
canine all the single ladies God damn
it your words are like knives Kyle
Canan